Now, assembled gods and goddesses, may I have your attention, please?
The difficulty level for this next salvation will be the dreaded us class.
And doing the honors this time will be...
The goddess Ristante.
I'm so glad it's you, Lista.
You have some big tasks ahead of you.
Once you finish this, you'll be a full-fledged, legitimate goddess.
Thank you all.
I vow to use this endeavor to better myself and gain experience so I can one day become a high-rinking goddess.
Are you freaking kidding me?
I can't believe they gave me an S-class job.
I'm Ristante, or Rista for short.
I was born into the unified divine realm, let's just say, 100 years ago.
I've summoned heroes from the human realm to save worlds on the brink of collapse five times so far.
But compared to the higher-level gods and goddesses, five times is nothing to brag about.
The average is about 10, and some of the big-deal deities have saved hundreds of worlds.
And in case you're wondering, S-class means that the world is so messed up and dangerous that even the most experienced gods don't want to go near it.
The last few times, I've chosen a young man from Japan to summon as the hero.
They seem the easiest to train.
Japan has a lot of stories about people being taken to another world for various reasons, so they get the idea pretty quickly.
And though the public is on the verge of being completely oversaturated with this kind of story, the sheer number of them can only mean it's still popular.
Wait, why am I narrating?
I'm so stressed, I'm losing my mind.
I can only summon one hero, so I have to choose carefully.
Suzuki, Sasaki.
Suzuki, Yamada.
Sasaki, Sato.
Suzuki, Tanaka, Sasaki, Yamada.
Sasaki, Suzuki, Yamada, Yamada.
Tanaka, Yamada, Sasaki, Suzuki.
Oh, jeez, they owe the light to me.
I need to make some kind of decision here.
Stupid paperwork.
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Hold on just a minute.
This guy is a level one, but his stats are unbelievably high.
Wow.
I've never seen a human with numbers like these before.
Oh, yes!
Whoever this is, he's a total phenom.
A one in a million find for sure.
No, he's more like a one in a hundred million find.
He'll be able to get Gea Brande back in order in no time,
and they'll be that much closer to being a super high-ranking goddess!
Oh, yes!
Heh! Yeah!
I'm the luckiest goddess there ever was!
Ha, ha, ha!
By the power of the goddess Restarte, I now summon a hero to the sacred chamber.
Come forth!
Seiya Ryugui!
Well, he's dreamy.
He's six feet tall with noble features under that luscious, dark hair, and it gives off an aura that's as heavenly as the great gods in the unified divine realm.
Oh, I could lose myself in passionate love with a man like this!
Wait! A goddess getting involved in a steamy romance with a human is uber-forbidden!
Ahem!
Greetings, I am the goddess known as Restarte.
I know this must be quite shocking, but it is out of urgent necessity that I have summoned you from the human world into our dimension.
Hearken to my words carefully, say Ryugui, and for you are the hero chosen to save the world of Gea Brande from the Demon Lord.
He's so enchanted by me that he can't even speak!
But I mean, who can blame him? I am a goddess after all.
And not to be vain, but I know I've got it going on.
What kind of freak drops a bomb like this on a stranger?
Who's a freak?! Are you talking about me?!
Oops! Calm down, Rista. A goddess must always maintain her composure.
Ahem! I'm sure that you must be mystified by me.
You've likely never been in the presence of a goddess such as me or summoned to a higher plane for a task such as this.
If you're really a goddess, couldn't you just save whatever the hell world it was by yourself?
Well, there are rules in place.
The gods have created countless worlds where the humans are to prosper by their own efforts.
This also means that these worlds where humans dwell must be saved by humans themselves.
What if I refuse?
This is a sacred duty.
I can't do as I please.
Not really.
Can I ask you to change the rules?
No, you cannot!
In other words, you're just using me. Lame.
This is gonna get old.
Now, now. He's overwhelmed. So take it easy on him.
It seems like most of these guys perk up when I start the next part.
Hey! How about you try calling out status?
Why?
Sorry. I suppose I just assumed that you were a gamer.
I'll explain. When you call out status, your abilities will magically appear before you in glowing numeric form.
Go on. Give it a whirl.
Properties.
Properties? No, we need you to say status, please!
Why would you say something else? Does that actually have meaning or...?
Sure enough, I see some data only I'd know about.
Which means that your ridiculous story may have a tiny shred of credibility.
You shouldn't be so rude to a goddess, you know?
Status! Just say status already!
Oh, please don't make me beg you to do it!
All right, status.
You see all that?
Your stat numbers are above and beyond any run-of-the-mill hero.
You're a one-in-a-hundred-million phenomenon!
There's only one hero who can defeat the Demon Lord of Gae Brande.
And that hero...
This you, Seiya!
You wanna tell me what happens if I die in this world?
What a wet blanket.
Not to worry.
You won't be able to return to Gae Brande.
You'll just be taken back to your world.
Huh. Not sold yet.
He sure is a tough nut to crack.
Maybe he has to see it for it to sink in.
In that case...
Seiya!
I'll explain everything in due time.
Open doorway to the other world!
Come, Seiya Ryugu-en!
Take my hand and follow me!
The fate of Gae Brande hinges on your spectacular heroic abilities!
No thanks.
This will be an exciting journey full of wonders and feats of...
Did you just say no?
Of course I said no.
You expect me to just rush into a fight with a demon?
Hold on a second!
I would have never chosen you if you didn't have a chance,
and I can provide backup whenever you need me to!
So you needn't worry.
I don't believe I can depend on your backup.
Have you totally forgotten you're talking to a goddess?!
I assure you that I will not let you die,
and if you were to get injured, I can use my healing magic on you!
That's not backup, and it's obvious you called me here
because you can't pull it off yourself.
What is this deal?!
I should bash in his beautiful, pretty face!
Listen up.
If I can't refuse, I gotta insist on one condition.
Well, what is it?
What do you want in return?
I mean...
Oh, I mustn't!
I truly hate to break your heart,
but love between gods and mortals is...
If I'm gonna do this, at least let me get prepared for it.
I need to be 100% ready.
What kind of hero is he?
Ben, like a bolt of lightning, it hit me.
I had overlooked a crucial personality trait.
Okay, so I can beat Ghost in Sherman
Okay...
We're so ready!
Oh,yeah!
Oh,yeah, oh,yeah!
Furnov LA, Oh,yeah!
Oh,yeah!
Oh,yeah, oh,yeah!
So!
キャツ про то 、最悪のソー
eES
EES
fact
uh
error
acious
Ú
labeled
eES
y
t
Play it smart
You got to lift the chance
The wise will take it all
Come here please
Now if the earth's gone
Sorry can't be you're the good
Handlawnしてく
人生の thoughts
安分が支配しとむ
You're ready
When all is good
If you're no place
耐えずして
時はもう満ちた
We're shot in
Oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
So
結晶とした光を
今こそ解放する
We're shot in
Oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
So
核心と栄光のスロー
核心と運命を始めよう
I never imagined that someone like this existed
Well how were things resolved in the end?
He's still training for it in an empty room at my place
A normal person would want to rush over and at least see another world right?
Rista your goal is to take control of Gaia Brande which is an S-Class mission
Perhaps a cautious attitude is most appropriate here
But it's such a colossal waste of time compared to going there and fighting some low-tier monsters
So he can start to get his XP level up
I promise it's okay
You don't need to be in such a rush
The flow of time is considerably slower in the Divine Realm than it is in the terrestrial worlds
I know but it's just that I want this adventure to work the way that it's supposed to
No matter your expectations he still needs your support
Which in this case means if he's busy training you need to be looking after him
What do you mean by that?
Like how are his living conditions?
Does he have a toilet and a place to shower?
Does he have a bed?
What have you given him to eat?
Now that you mention it
And be sure to keep in mind if you're giving him orders and reminding him you're a goddess
He may not respond that well
He might be more agreeable if you treated him as a friend
You're right as always, Aria
I knew I could count on you
Another pep talk right on schedule
Hey! I'm so sorry for leaving you here all by your-
Holy six-pack
Yo, does the concept of knocking not exist here or what?
Oh, whoops!
Wait a minute, this is my place after all
I bet you're hungry
What's that?
Well, since you're Japanese, I brought you some rice bowls
This one is pickled plum and this one has some yummy salmon
I was raised to never accept food from weird strangers
I am not a stranger so would you stop being so rude!
You should eat it first
Why?
I need to be sure that it's not poisoned
What reason would I have to poison you?
You see, it's just fine
Why in the room would I try to kill you?
Okay, so there's no fast-acting poison in them
No slow-acting poison either!
Oh, and FYI
Push-ups, pull-ups, and sit-ups don't do anything to increase your stats
I'll leave three meals a day outside your door, but I won't bother you
When you're finally ready, you can call me with this
Until you call me, I promise to leave you in complete solitude, okay?
What?
Is that not enough for you?
How do I know that this won't trigger an explosive?
Well, he can do whatever he pleases in there
I give it three days tops before he buzzes me
Still no buzz
Is it broken?
Or did something else happen?
It could be bad
He's dead!
But he is eating the food I leave him
I guess I'll just keep on waiting
It's never gonna ring
I'll have to wait forever
You ring!
Sexy, so fresh and so clean
I remember telling you to knock first
Yeah, I'm the rude one here
So how's the training going?
Status
You leveled up like crazy just from working out?
You do have that unique XP boost skill after all
I know you have other special skills
If it were completely up to me, I'd like to max out my levels first
You'd spend the rest of your life in here!
Time passes slowly in this realm, but we don't have forever
We have to get going
On to Gaia Brande!
Yeah, okay
I am perfectly prepared
I am 100% ready for this
What is he doing?
Trying to work in some cool little catchphrase?
Great!
But you don't have to say that
Let's just go already!
The great goddess Ishtar determined this was the perfect place for us to enter this world
Now, we need to go into the town of Idona and get your equipment
Hello! You just passing through?
Hello! Yes we are!
Are you sure it's safe to be casually walking around this strange village when you're dressed like a stripper?
Watch your mouth, pal!
And I use my goddess power to make it look like I'm wearing normal clothes
I'm not nearly as concerned about your outfit as I am about that man
He could well be a monster in disguise
Jeez, he's just a regular guy
I don't like the look of him
It's possible he's a shapeshifter
No, it's not
Even if he's not literally a monster, he could be a thief or a mass murderer
I may need to take him out before he kills us
You're the one who sounds like a murderer, you paranoid weirdo!
Oh wow, you sure look super pretty in that outfit, lady
You're like a goddess or something
How sweet!
And I said little children can always recognize true beauty
Mister, you got some funny clothes but you seem really cool anyway
My, are you gonna let some childish remark upset you?
I bet they call you Mister Cool
What's your real name?
It's Saya
Oh, my name's Nina, nice to meet you
I'd love to watch this interaction go on but we have a job to do
Oh tell me, Nina, is there a blacksmith or weapon shop nearby?
Yeah, there's a place like that real close
Just a little bit down the road that way
Thanks Nina, I appreciate it
Here's a little present from me to you
This should be more than enough money to buy whatever you think you're gonna need
Welcome
Definitely gonna take this steel armor right here
Nice, excellent choice
Three sets
Not so fast!
You don't need that much armor!
I do because I need one to wear, one for spare, and one more in case the spare needs a spare
Do you have an armor fetish?
What kind of ridiculous hero spends all his money on three identical sets of armor?
I'll choose one for you, so just stay put, okay?
You're not the boss of me
He's not just cautious, he's pathological
Mmm, that's way better
You really look like the ideal hero to me
I need 30 smoke bombs, 50 medicinal herbs, and 50 anecdotal herbs
Oh, yes, coming right up, sir
Thank you
At least they're not that expensive
But still, you bought so many
There's no telling what we might encounter
So I need to be prepared
I may not look it, but I am a veteran at this stuff
Therefore, I located the perfect starting place for you
There's nothing but weak monsters around here
I'm not so sure, and I highly doubt you're a veteran like you claim
Why would I be lying?
She's right
It's true
Even I can walk over to the next town with no problem at all
Only things we gotta deal with are wibbly wobbly little slimes
If a cute little girl can handle it, then so can you
Does that put your mind at ease?
You look pretty strong, Mr. Seiya
Are you really afraid of going outside of town?
Yeah, underneath all that armor, he's actually just a big, strong, fraidy cat
Well then, take this
This charm will ward off any evil
You didn't put a curse on this, did you?
Jeez! Just stop it!
What'd you say?
Don't pay any attention to him, he's just a little sick
Nina, what have you got into?
Hey, Papa!
I apologize, my daughter can be a little nosy
I'm sorry if she bothered you
No, no, not at all
Right?
No, not very much at least
Hmm, so he's not completely disagreeable
Okay, it's finally monster fight o'clock!
I don't see any good reason why we need to go out looking for trouble
Don't be such a diaper baby!
You have enough gear to take on an army!
There's a little monster!
I've never seen anything like that before
Are they genetically engineered?
Don't you know what a slime is?
These things are in like every game
Nope
You are really Japanese, right?
Slimes jump at you when they attack
But they're so weak that practically anyone can kill them with just a stick!
So...
Hey!
What are you doing?
Ah!
Now!
Atomic Split Slash!
Overkill much?
It's just the slime!
They're like the easiest thing to beat!
I'm not done!
I'm afraid it may still be alive!
Casting Hell's Fire!
The slime has gone okay so just cut it out!
No, not yet.
There could still be danger
Huh?
You mean you know more than two special attacks already?
How about another Atomic Split Slash attack?
Why use the same attack twice in a row like that?
Uh-uh!
Have another Hell's Fire!
Of course you'd have to use that one again!
It can't be more dead!
Stop!
We get it!
Atomic Split Slash!
Done.
That was just a slime!
You vaporized it on the first Atomic whatever!
Always be on guard.
No, not always!
Honestly, Seiya, I mean you do already have the scan ability, right?
Use that to check the slime stats!
I did check them, Kay.
Its attack and defense were both in the single digits.
Then why did you throw everything at it?
There could be more to it than just the visible data.
Try to have some more faith in your skills!
Anyway, I hope this boosted your confidence a bit, Seiya.
Look, you have incredible power and all the equipment that you would possibly need, so let's...
Oh, what's that?
Very impressive swordsmanship.
You're the one, right?
Yes, you must be the one.
Wait, who are you?
Pleased to make your acquaintance fair, goddess and brave hero.
Welcome!
I'm one of four heavenly kings serving the demon lord.
I am known as Chaos Machina!
What? No way, you can't be!
We're not supposed to be facing a powerful enemy yet!
You sound quite surprised.
Our wise demon lord detected the signs of a hero's summoning before it even happened.
So comically predictable.
Every time a new hero is summoned, they head to an area full of the weakest monsters to boost their skills.
And when I thought about where that might be...
I knew this was the perfect spot to end you!
Now I see why this is an S-class mission.
I can't use any of my normal strategies.
The demon lord has been vigilantly waiting for a hero to appear.
I didn't think we needed to worry, but here we are.
And now that I look at you...
I can tell you're something special.
Deep within you lies the potential to be an incredibly powerful foe.
It's too bad.
That won't do.
No, no, no, no, no.
It just won't do at all!
I'll have to end you right now!
Oh no! I need to scan her right away!
Why are we going up against someone this powerful in the first stage?
How do we get out of this?
I guess we should try to run as fast as we can, but then what?
What do you think, Seiya?
Huh?
Later!
He lost me!
Hey, sweetie! What's the big idea?
Running away without thinking is the smart thing to do.
Most humans wouldn't be so decisive when faced with danger.
Well, how fascinating.
Yes, what a fascinating hero!
Wait for me!
You'd run away and leave a goddess behind!
AAAAAA!
Let's go!